📱(Satori Shun) Today
Let's break down the fake love relationship.
(Hattori Maika) What?
(Photo) What Shun says ➡
What I stopped listening to
Is it your fault?
Shun's feelings
Would you like to respect it?
(Photo) Be aware of your body.
For Shun
What can we do?
(Akiyama) What Hattori can do
There are still.
♬〜
⚟Shun! Ha ha ha...
i got you. Hmm...
♬〜
Why….
Because ➡
Again like back then ➡
Maybe I'm going somewhere
That's what I was thinking.
♬〜
Maika...
sorry.
When we first met ➡
immediately
I realized that it was Hattori Maika.
What I was dumped by you
I was dragging it on ➡
I'm thinking of trying to get revenge
I've come near you.
Shun-san...
But in my mind ➡
I hate you more
I was thinking it but ➡
It was different.
Why did we meet again in high school?
Did you get attracted to you?
I remembered clearly.
(Kozue/Recollection)⦅Can I borrow a note? ⦆
⦅Ah, that's good⦆
(Kozue) ｟I did it~ Thank you! ｠
Bright and kind ➡
On equal terms with everyone ➡
Straight...
♬〜
That time and now...
You are still as wonderful as ever.
♬〜
I was saved by you again.
thank you.
♬〜
But I'm involved in my own problem
sorry.
♬〜
this….
Sorry I'm late to reply.
Huh?
I….
I was saved by Kagaya-kun.
♬〜
Become friends with Kagaya-kun ➡
Every day was fun.
I'm looking forward to it
More and more books I like ➡
after that….
｟I like it｠
I was also happy about the confession.
♬〜
but….
I was back then ➡
I don't have confidence in myself...
Me ➡
To Kagaya-kun
I thought it wasn't suitable.
♬〜
So...
no matter what
I couldn't come here.
Even now
I don't think it's appropriate.
♬〜
but….
I'm still...
I like you.
Shu... Shun?
"It's not worth it"...
I thought it was a line to me.
Huh?
I like it.
♬〜
Now ➡
Do this
It's like being touched by Maika...
It's like a dream.
♬〜
He appeared in front of me again➡
thank you.
♬〜
Maika.
Shun-san.
♬〜
i love you.
Me too.
♬〜
(Voice of the heart)
⚟Maika ready?
Ah yes.
♬〜
Yes, it's cute today too.
I'm going to do it
It's been a while since I went to a nostalgic town ➡
Why not explore together?
Huh?
Is it okay?
Yeah.
♬〜
Huh?
Wasn't there an elementary school around here?
Ahhh, it's beyond here.
I came from that elementary school.
Wow.
So is your parents' house nearby?
Ahhh, that's right. Ours...
⚞(Naomi) Maika-chan?
mother….
Huh?
(Naomi) Maika-chan!
Why are you here?
Ah, no, that...
(Naomi) Who is this person?
Ah, nice to meet you.
Meet Maika
I'm doing it ➡
My name is Satori Shun.
Let's meet...
Sorry but you
I wonder what kind of work you're doing.
With Maika
I work for the same company.
"Bird Left"...
What the president?‡
Isn't it amazing? ➡
Maika If you're such a wonderful person ➡
Mom and dad agree.
mother.
(Naomi) The guy before was ➡
As a regular employee
It wasn't even there, right? ➡
I was worried.
But I'm relieved. ➡
Maika too
He was shrewd.
mother
A bit of a way to say that...
(Naomi)
Since we're going to have it, please come and visit us. ➡
A story about work
What about the plans for the two of you in the future?
I want to ask.
Ah, no, um...
Ah, actually, Maika and I are
I've come here for work.
Immediately to work now
I have to go back.
(Naomi) Oh, is that so?
yes.
Re-date the day
I'll come to you to say hello.
(Naomi) That's right. That's a shame.
Excuse me then.
let's go.
(Naomi)
Don't let go, Maika-chan.
sorry
That's so obvious.
My mother has been around for a long time...
People are titled and public figures
There's something to judge.
When I'm with my mother ➡
I feel like I'm choking up.
It's the same as me.
Huh?
no….
Mother is
I'm worried about Maika.
I agree….
It's my mother's love
I know that...
♬〜
I'm now ➡
This is how we can be together
I'm happy.
Me too.
♬〜
Let's stay together forever.
yes.
♬〜
So, officially
I started dating ➡
Is that what you mean?
ah. Now I'll work too➡
I think I can try harder.
A very soft look
It's starting to happen.
Huh?
It's Hattori's influence.
Ah...
Did I look so strict?
Yeah. Haha. But ➡
Looks happy now
I'm happy too.
ah.
Oh, it's about time.
Development materials for "Hoshikawa Resort"
Is it all here?
yes. Just to be safe, Hikari Gen Real Estate
I've also got the data... ➡
Ah, that's right. And ➡
Miss Photon did this.
A matchmaking photo?
(Akiyama) Yes. ➡
The other day, I went out of my way
Come to the company to deliver it.
Mitsuko-sama also for Hattori-san
I don't think I'll do anything.
I think it's better to be careful.
It's okay.
I'll definitely protect her.
It's over!
(Mashima) Is it over? Amazing.
yes. Ah, but today ➡
"Kumai Consulting"
We also have to get the case data.
(Mashima) You're so enthusiastic.
Has something good happened?
Ah, no.
Anyway, I want to do my best.
(Mashima) That's reliable. Well then
Please make an announcement at the next meeting.
yes. Ah, it's almost time.
(Mashima) Ah. Okay.
📱(Message incoming call/manner mode)
(Shun's voice) "Tonight
Don't you eat at home? ”
(Mashima) Are you ready?
Ah yes!
♬〜
⚟Ping Ping Ping Ping (Interhoon)
please.
Ah...
Sorry I'm late. that…
Meetings lasted a long time.
Even if you don't hurry that much
That's good.
I'm
I got my work done early today.
But I wanted to meet soon.
♬〜
I see. thank you.
Wow, amazing! Looks tasty.
Something...➡
From what
Have it prepared.
Next time I'll help out too.
That's fine, I have plenty of room for this kind of thing
Someone should do it.
♬〜
Yes, eat it.
Ah, thank you very much.
Ah, this too. yes.
already~
Shun-san, you're spoiling me too much.
Haha.
So next time I'll be pampered.
On weekends, I'm at Maika's house
Maybe I'll make something.
That's good. What do you want to eat?
That's right... hmm...
📱
I'm a bit sorry.
Tap (Mobile operation sound)
what up?
📱 (Akiyama) President ➡
Where to go
very sorry.
Has something happened?
📱(Akiyama) Actually, I just said ➡
I received a call from my North American branch.
yeah?
Has something happened?
ah.
Starting tomorrow, New York
I was going on a business trip.
What, starting tomorrow?
Apparently it's a problem when signing a contract ➡
If it stays like this
The transaction could turn back to blank.
For at least two weeks
I think I'll be staying.
That's right.
Sorry I can't be with you on the weekend.
Ah...
It's a little sad, but...
But while I'm away
I'll polish my cooking skills.
thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
(Director) Actually, please give an order from above. ➡
Sorry for the sudden question ➡
Smart hotel
For the project ➡
From launch
I was to be involved. ➡
I'll be in Osaka in two weeks
You will have to be transferred.
yes….
From next week
That's quite a sudden story.
That's right.
But it was good.
The transfer destination is Big Project
The management team, right?
yes.
But...➡
Why was I chosen...
(Mashima) Someone
Didn't you rate it?
Be confident!
<<What you can challenge at work?
I'm happy but ➡
Long distance between you and Shun...≫
While Shun was away ➡
I'm going to Osaka.
📱(Message incoming call/manner mode)
Huh?
What happened?
Maika will be transferred to Osaka
Did you know?
Is it Osaka?
Ah... I'm sorry
I didn't know.
Something is wrong.
This business trip suddenly came along...
📱(Manner mode)
Tap
hello.
About transfers
Sorry I can't figure it out.
Maybe
To separate me and Maika ➡
My mother is
It may be something that was set up.
Right... what is it?
I'll check it out when I return to Japan.
As soon as possible you
I'll try to move so I can go back to the head office.
📱 That's why...
No, it's fine.
Huh?
If it was your mother's instructions ➡
I've even more like this project
I want to get through it until the end.
Maika...
I want to get good results.
I want to be recognized by my mother too.
📱 Me➡
More to a woman worthy of Shun
I want to be.
No...➡
I'm fine as it is now though.
but….
Yeah. If you think so
I'll give you all the support.
thank you.
I just promised not to overdo it.
yes.
♬〜
I've come from Tokyo Head Office
This is Hattori Maika.
With you all, as soon as possible
To ensure that you are in alignment ➡
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Clap clap clap...
(Employees) Please!
♬〜
Click (click sound)
💻 Poron (error sound)
♬〜
Click
💻 Polon
<Eh?
This system is different from the head office.
⚟(Yugo) Hattori-san.
Ha... Yes.
(Yugo) Don't you know anything?
Ah, um...➡
Where is this number?
Should I enter it?
Ah, is that okay? ➡
Umm...
(Yugo) Yes, it's here.
Ah, thank you very much.
Ah, uh...
(Yugo) Ah, of the same team ➡
This is Kato Yugo.
thank you.
How to open the system
It's different from the head office, so it's so frustrating.
Huh?
(Yugo) Oh, I too, until a few years ago.
I was at the head office.
I've been in Kansai since I was transferred.
That's right.
At first, there are a lot of different things
It's going to be difficult though ➡
Don't be too nervous
Let's do it together.
Yes, thank you very much.
Ah, and
A delicious okonomiyaki restaurant ➡
Udon restaurants and more
There are a lot ➡
If you want to know
Please listen at any time.
yes.
(Nozomi) It's going to be soooo. ➡
Hattori-san
That's where I'll go and squeal.
Ahh, Ah, I see... what is it?
(Nozomi) No lie No.
This is Asaka. Thank you very much.
Ah, thank you very much.
(Nozomi) If you have any questions ➡
Listen to me not to hesitate.
Yes, thank you very much.
(Nozomi) Oh.
(Yugo)
Have you relieved your tension a little?
Ah yes.
Thanks to something
It feels like it's suddenly loosened.
⚞(Boss)
Hattori-san, is that a bit okay?
Ah yes.
♬〜
(Boss) I did it in the middle, is it okay?
Ah, it's okay.
♬〜
If you have any problems
Please ask anything.
Being separated
I wonder how long it will last.
When there's someone you can trust nearby ➡
I don't need to bear it
Because there isn't.
Not the president
I want you to choose me.